sup everyone Tim was only five through
the very special video today I got were
calling for you [ __ ] I got myself
some zat's browsers that's Bell TCG car
game compacts that bomb I'm in it now
you're probably wondering 10:05 wha well
that's simple question there are two
characters in the sass bill anime and
they look a lot like I mean Allah Akbar
but I even do a piece of fan about here
you go out there
two characters the names on Raycom in
maru's respectively they might be lost
talking about me so I actually shipped
them back when I used to watch the moon
it was like on I don't like Nickelodeon
some shine your [ __ ] where anyways yeah
that's pitiless to this [ __ ] it costs a
lot cause like 80 bucks and [ __ ] but
it's a price of the price I pay because
it smells I paid because I love about
dark and [ __ ] so we're gonna get started
I'm hoping to pull ray calm and morose
if I don't I'm gonna be pissed the kids
i'd mainly want the array calm Mauro's
and fame
because they say no mafia Sonya so I put
a picture of him so I'll show you
so yeah cuz I with the foot pack and
[ __ ] come on I can get this [ __ ] that's
not rake on my loose I don't want this
[ __ ] oh my God oh that's that's that's
what that's Sonia that's fine I uh
watching this isn't her character cut
his character card this is a spell that
fain can use and [ __ ] so that kind of
sucks cuz I can't use that [ __ ] I mean
they but instead of Ray Comoros and Fang
they gave me hollows and they think they
think that she makes me happy
no and you know look like that I don't
want that [ __ ] I don't want that [ __ ] I
see [ __ ] pain now I won't take on the
road so yeah cause the next pack [ __ ]
come on oh [ __ ] the [ __ ] what the [ __ ]
oh [ __ ] I got these two I mean talk
about these two yet this your mom India
Manic yeah and [ __ ] so but it's not no
ray Comoros so how many packs on you got
away I got three more packs just three
I'm not gonna get this Jemma I can
complain out on my Gary funny [ __ ] so
yeah oh my God give me the good [ __ ]
come on oh my [ __ ] God oh my God are
you kidding me this is the fat [ __ ]
these are like a test of fates pay him
here we go
this has to be either ray Comoros this
oh [ __ ]
is the spells - oh my [ __ ] oh my God
there it is oh my God they so cool oh
[ __ ] I don't even watch this show I mean
I did bus stop watch I kept so world
life that [ __ ] die oh my God oh [ __ ] oh
my God that's cool
damn what do they do oh my God Bobby K
no gay effects ok sock [ __ ] it sorry
guys 1000 power tool
who's got power equipped it oh my God
damn [ __ ] almost down oh [ __ ]
we did it guys we got it